LStand 0
RStand 5
Wait 1
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Mr. Unicorn. Can you tell me more things in the past?  
Say 1 1 Unicorn In the past...fine! 
Say 1 0 Unicorn About more than 1 year ago, Her Majesty arrived at this island.  
Say 1 0 Unicorn She came here to look for the one she loved deeply... 
Say 1 0 Unicorn But, he ruthlessly denied Her Majesty.  
Say 1 0 Unicorn I saw Her Majesty crying every day and couldn't bear to let it be.   
Say 1 1 Unicorn So, I helped her kill the bad guy.  
Say 1 1 Unicorn Afterwards, I helped her seize the throne of the island and made her the queen.  
Say 1 0 Unicorn I thought it would make her happy, but... 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor But, no gold or jewelry is able to make the queen smile again, isn't it? 
Say 1 0 Unicorn ...
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor So, who is the one who was not loyal to the queen's love?  
Say 1 1 Unicorn Well...I can't tell you. 
Say 1 1 Unicorn You should not ask it again...It is the secret of the queen.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! The more secret it is, the more interested I'm.  
Say 1 0 Unicorn ...
