RStand 1
Wait 1
Say 1 2 Greedy_King Kill them! Kill all these poor people!  
Say 1 2 Greedy_King I have to collect their souls, or that lord will be angry!! 
LSet 0
LIn
Wait 1
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Your Majesty, nice to meet you! 
Say 1 2 Greedy_King It is you again!!!
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Why does Your Majesty begin to slaughter poor people? 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Please don't chop off their heads when you kill them, or they can't be made zombies.  
Say 1 1 Greedy_King I beg you. Take all my gold and leave.  
Say 1 1 Greedy_King I just want the souls, or I will be killed!  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Killed? 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor When our Black Heart King made the deal with the "Demon".
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Why didn't you expect the coming of this day?
RFace 3
Say 1 2 Greedy_King I...I have no idea what you are talking about! 
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Since Your Majesty has no idea, let my zombies remind you of it. 