LStand 0
Wait 1
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor The Knight Commander runs so fast. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor He disappears in an eyewink...
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Aha! There is he!  
RSet 2
RIn
Wait 1
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Honored knight commander, I find you finally.  
Say 1 1 Knight_Long ...
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor You haven't told me what you are collecting in the Suicide Forest?  
Say 1 0 Knight_Long Since we have an agreement, it is ok to tell you. 
Say 1 1 Knight_Long The only thing which can be collected in the Suicide Forest and the miners' graves is soul. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Just like what is in my mind. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor So, what will Black Heart King do with such souls?  
Say 1 1 Knight_Long Well...I don't know.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! You don't know it? Then why are you collecting them?
Say 1 1 Knight_Long I...I'm just performing my duties. 
Say 1 1 Knight_Long As the Knight Commander, I have to obey all orders of his majesty! 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! You'll execute all his orders without asking anything, won't you? 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor If Black Heart King orders you to kill yourself, will you obey his order? 
Say 1 2 Knight_Long You...you are humiliating me! 
Say 1 2 Knight_Long I'll fight with you again！
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor No problem. \n Come on! Zombies! 
