LStand 0
RStand 5
Wait 1
Say 1 0 Unicorn ...
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! There is a unicorn!  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Is my dear witch here?  
Say 1 0 Unicorn Stranger, leave here immediately... 
Say 0 2 Devil_Doctor Oh-oh! A unicorn can speak human language?!  
Say 1 0 Unicorn Hum! I'm not an ordinary unicorn.  
Say 1 1 Unicorn I'm the most loyal servant of Ice Queen.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! You are the servant of the beautiful queen.  
Say 1 2 Unicorn How dare you! \n Don't call Her Majesty this way!   
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! It seems none of the residents on this island are hospitable.   
Say 1 2 Unicorn Everyone who insults Her Majesty has to die!!  
