LStand 0
RStand 4
Wait 1
Say 1 2 Death_Witch Tut-tut. It is you again!  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor My dear witch, it takes me so much time to chase you.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor But I miss it. Ten years ago, I chased you just like this, didn't I?  
Say 1 1 Death_Witch Alas! Ten years has passed. You are still behaving in such an irritating style.
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor But you said you didn't like zombies and denied me ten years ago.  
Say 1 0 Death_Witch Exactly. Zombies are so disgusting. 
Say 1 0 Death_Witch My monsters are much more lovely.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor That's not true...I think zombies are also very lovely. 
Say 1 0 Death_Witch So we are unable to get along with one another. Leave me alone.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor ...
