LStand 0
Wait 1
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor What a large marsh!  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! It seems somebody is coming over.  
RSet 2
RIn
Wait 1
Say 1 1 Knight_Long You must be Evil Doctor who has bullied His Majesty. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! That's me!  
Say 1 1 Knight_Long Hum! You are frank. 
Say 1 0 Knight_Long I'm the Knight Commander of the garrison. 
Say 1 1 Knight_Long You have illegally used zombies to attack and loot villages.   
Say 1 2 Knight_Long I'm now here to perform your execution according to the law! 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! I'm suddenly sentenced to death. How exciting it is!  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor However, my zombies won't approve it.  
Say 1 0 Knight_Long 've no time to hear your wisecracks. Let your zombies fight me. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! As you wish. 
