LStand 0
Wait 1
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Oh dear! There are so many corpses in the forest.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor It seems to be suitable for being reconstructed to zombie farmland.   
RSet 2
RIn
Wait 1
Say 1 0 Knight_Long It used to be called the Suicide Forest.  
Say 1 1 Knight_Long The miners who lost home and wealth would come to the forest to kill themselves.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! We meet again. Young knight commander.  
Say 1 0 Knight_Long Hello! It is a small world. Evil Doctor!  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Our righteous Knight Commander, I don't know what you are doing here.  
Say 1 0 Knight_Long Under the order of His Majesty, I'm here to collect something. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor What is it? 
Say 1 0 Knight_Long I can't tell you. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! If I defeat you, will you tell me? 
Say 1 0 Knight_Long Fine! Bring it on! 
