LStand 0
Wait 1
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Oh-oh! Why are there no people here in the gold mine?  
RSet 1
RIn
Wait 1
Say 1 1 Greedy_King Hum! Of course not! All the gold here has been exploited many years ago.  
Say 1 0 Greedy_King An abandoned gold mine. No one will be interested.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! I'd better go to loot another town!  
Say 1 2 Greedy_King Wait! I'm here to avenge the insult I suffered before. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Avenge the insult? 
Say 1 1 Greedy_King You've defeated my army several times. I'll achieve the victory this time.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Let me bring you more loss of gold coins!  
RFace 3
Say 1 2 Greedy_King Cut the crap! Show me what you got!  