LStand 0
RStand 2
Wait 1
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Our young Knight Commander. Nice to meet you again.  
Say 1 0 Knight_Long Doctor... 
Say 1 1 Knight_Long I asked His Majesty about the use of souls... 
Say 1 0 Knight_Long  But, His Majesty was reluctant to answer me... 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem. Actually, I have a near guess. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Let me tell you about it, OK? 
Say 1 0 Knight_Long Please... 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor The reason why I like zombies is because zombies have no mind.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Without souls but just bodies, they can still move and attack.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor On the contrary, souls are useless for me. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor They are not edible and can't kill.
Say 1 0 Knight_Long So...
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Souls have a certain value - be used to deal with demon. 
Say 1 0 Knight_Long You mean His Majesty has made a deal with demon?!  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Believe it or not, it is up to you! 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Conversation is over. I have to loot gold coins in the next city.  
Say 1 0 Knight_Long So...sorry! I can't let you pass. 
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Even if your Black Heart King is making a deal with demon.
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor You still make up your mind to be loyal to him?
Say 1 0 Knight_Long ...This is the fate of a knight. I can't disobey it.  
Say 0 2 Devil_Doctor Fine. Zombies, be prepared for fight!  
