LStand 0
RStand 6
Wait 1
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Beautiful queen, nice to meet you!  
Say 1 0 Ice_Queen Hum! Nasty being, what are you doing here in the Hot Spring City? 
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor I'm coming here to meet Your Majesty.  
Say 1 1 Ice_Queen If you want to propose again, save it. I won't accept it.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem. That's not my purpose this time.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor This time, I'm here to hear the story about the unicorn and white bear.  
Say 1 1 Ice_Queen Hum...The boring brothers, biting one another. I have no interests in them.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor So, it was you that changed them into a unicorn and a polar bear? 
Say 1 0 Ice_Queen Yes, it was me.  
Say 1 0 Ice_Queen I have changed a number of people into animals.  
Say 1 1 Ice_Queen Most of the people who intended to pay court to me have been changed into animals.
Say 1 1 Ice_Queen Including those two.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor But why is Mr. Unicorn still following you wholeheartedly?    
Say 1 0 Ice_Queen Hum! The nasty being hopes to become my slave, doesn't he?  
Say 1 0 Ice_Queen He said he loved me and he wanted to prove it.  
Say 1 1 Ice_Queen I told him to let me change him into an animal.
Say 1 1 Become my slave and give the whole kingdom tome.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor As a result, he did it. Ahem! What a silly kid.  
Say 1 2 Ice_Queen Yes, extremely silly.\n He abandoned his dignity as a human for the illusory sentiment.  
Say 1 2 Ice_Queen What a nasty being!  
Say 1 0 Ice_Queen He thought it would get my sympathy and compassion.
Say 1 0 But in fact, he only gets my mock and contempt. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! What a pathetic life!  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Suddenly, I feel I am 1,000 times as lucky as he is.  
Say 1 0 Ice_Queen Oh？
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor I won't betray myself for anyone.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor In my world, only zombies and gold really matter.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! We have something in common to this aspect, don't we?  
Say 1 0 Ice_Queen Hum! Indeed. You are one of the best nasty beings.  
Say 1 2 Ice_Queen But, you are a still nasty! I won't have a second look at you. It will make my eyes dirty!  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Then, let me show you the power of my zombie army!  