LStand 0
RStand 7
Wait 1
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear Growl! Growl! You are finally here.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Nothing can hold back my curiosity.  
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear Growl! Growl! Have a seat and I'll tell you the story.  
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear After I arrived at this island.
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear I built this kingdom together with my first mate and also my best friend.  
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear Afterwards, I married a beautiful wife and lived a happy life.  
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear But, good times didn't last long.
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear My wife was suddenly attacked by a strange disease and passed away.
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear I was too sad to care for the affairs of the kingdom and lived a muddleheaded life.  
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear At that, the kingdom became worse and worse. 
Say 1 1 Famine and disease plagued the island.   
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear One day, Ice Queen suddenly appeared.  
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear My good friend, the mate, betrayed me and fell in love with Ice Queen.  
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear He could do anything for Ice Queen. Even let Ice and Snow make him a unicorn.  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor So you are talking about the speaking unicorn I have met?  
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear Yes, it is him. Growl!  
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear For Ice and Snow, he betrayed his family, friends, nation and race.  
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear At last, he helped Ice and Snow initiate a coup.  
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear The masses who suffered from hunger.
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear And poverty supported Ice Queen as their new queen.  
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear While, I had been changed to a polar bear by Ice and Snow with her witchcraft.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! A bear kingdom, sounds like an interesting story!  
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear People on this island have gradually forgotten me...  
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear Only the animals still remember me.  
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor So, you go to visit the animals very often. Ahem!  
Say 1 1 Snow_Bear Growl! Growl! My story is over. It is not moving or touching, is it?  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Ahem! It is fine.  
Say 1 0 Snow_Bear Ok, are you ready for the fight?  
Say 0 1 Devil_Doctor Fight? 
Say 1 2 Snow_Bear Since your zombie army has arrived at the palace of the old king.
Say 1 2 Snow_Bear There is no reason to avoid the fight! Growl! 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! As you wish! 
