RStand 2
Wait 1
Say 1 1 Knight_Long ...
Say 1 1 Knight_Long What the hell are I doing...?
Say 1 1 Knight_Long Is what I am doing just...? 
LSet 0
LIn
Wait 1
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Of course not.
Say 1 2 Knight_Long !!!
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Why is there no living person in this village? 
Say 1 1 Knight_Long Because the gold fever vanished. This nameless village has already been abandoned. 
Say 1 0 Knight_Long All young people have left it for other cities.  
Say 1 0 Knight_Long The aged who stayed in the village died successively afterwards...
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem. This is an ideal place to plant zombies! 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Also an ideal place for you to collect souls, isn't it? 
Say 1 0 Knight_Long ...
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Knight Commander! Do you know how to use the souls of the dead? 
Say 1 0 Knight_Long I have no idea...
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor In essence, a living person consists of two parts, body and soul.
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor One who loses his soul becomes a zombie. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! Collecting souls is just the same as my planting of zombies in essence. 
Say 1 2 Knight_Long Impossible... 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor You really should go back to ask your Black Heart King what he will do with such souls. 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Perhaps, he is more evil than devil Doctor. Ahem!  
Say 1 2 Knight_Long Please do not insult his majesty!!! 
Say 0 0 Devil_Doctor Ahem! You seem to be angry. Let's start the war!  
